Guide to Megan O'Shea's One Resource to Rule Them All MOS.2021
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Megan O'Shea's "One Resource to Rule Them All"
2016-2021, undated
2020-2021, undated
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Megan O'Shea
Debs, Eugene V. (Eugene Victor), 1855-1926
Belfrage family
Tamiment Library
Weatherly Stephan
MOS.2021
25 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder 24" x 24"
This is the abstract. It has a title in it.
This is the physical facet of the collection.
10
Conditions Governing Access
This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
The following chronology provides a backdrop for the Board of Higher Education of the City of New York cases included within this collection:
1939 The New York State Legislature enacted Section 12-a of the Civil Service Law which provided in substance that "no person shall be appointed to or retained in the public service nor in any public educational institution who becomes a member of any organization which advocates the overthrow of government by force or violence, or by any unlawful means (L. 1939, Ch. 547)."
Abbreviation Expansion
MIT
Massachusetts Institute of Technology
PCV
Peace Corps Volunteer
Ordered List
This is a citation for Weatherly Stephan's Journal of Archival Organization article.
I don't know why on earth you'd put a line break in an ordered list,
but here ya go.
Copyright New York University, all rights reserved.
This is just a name name with no identity.
Accruals Note
This is the Accruals note.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
Appraisal
This is the Appraisal note.
Arrangement
This is the Arrangement note.
Biographical Note
This is the Biographical note.
Custodial History
This is the Custodial History note.
General
This is the General note.
Elmer Holmes Bobst Library
70 Washington Square South
2nd Floor
New York, NY 10012
special.collections@nyu.edu
URL:
ALS
The Sally Belfrage Papers (TAM 189)
Ardouin, Charles Nicholas Celigny. Essais sur l'histoire d'Haiti. Port-au-Prince, 1865.
No doubt the estate has exerted a tremendous influence on the development of my character. One may walk for an hour without glimpsing another soul, which has taught me to love tranquility.
Tamiment Library March 2021
Abbreviation Expansion
MIT
Massachusetts Institute of Technology
Oral histories (literary works) Court records |z New York (State) Motion pictures |x Production and direction. Court records |z New York (State) |z Kings County Court records |z New York (State) |z Queens County Land titles |z New York (State) |z Kings County Cooking |v Periodicals Cooking -- Periodicals Rolodex MOS.2021 Fulbright scholars. Irish American women -- History -- 19th century.
Existence and Location of Originals
This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
Other Finding Aids
This is the Other Finding Aids note.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
Related Materials
This is the Related Materials note. Those using the collection may also be interested in P132, held in this repository, which includes photographs of Pemberly, Darcy's estate and childhood home. In an April 1795 letter to his friend, Charles Bingley, Darcy wrote
No doubt the estate has exerted a tremendous influence on the development of my character. One may walk for an hour without glimpsing another soul, which has taught me to love tranquility.
The Sally Belfrage Papers (TAM 189)
Scope and Content
This is the Scope and Content note.
Separated Materials
This is the Separated Materials note.
Existence and Location of Copies
This is the Existence and Location of Copies note.
Bibliography
This is the Bibliography.
Adler, Jerry. High Rise.New York:
Harper Collins, 1993.
Corruption and Racketeering in the New York City Construction Industry. Interim Report by the New York State Organized Crime Task Force. Ithaca, NY: ILR Press, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University, 1988.
Corruption and Racketeering in the New York City Construction Industry. Final Report to Governor Mario M. Cuomo. Ronald Goldstock, Director, New York State Organized Crime Task Force. December 1989.
Ardouin, Charles Nicholas Celigny. Essais sur l'histoire d'Haiti. Port-au-Prince, 1865.
Boston (Mass.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; New York (N.Y.) |x History; New York (N.Y.) |x Intellectual life |y 20th century; New York (N.Y.) |x Intellectual life; New York (N.Y.) |x Mass transit.; New York (N.Y.) |x Museums.; New York (N.Y.) |x Officials and employees |v Portraits.; New York (N.Y.) |x Officials and employees.; New York (N.Y.) |x Officials and employees; New York (N.Y.) |x Politics and government; New York (N.Y.) |x Religious life and customs; New York (N.Y.) |x Social conditions |y 20th century.; New York (N.Y.) |x Social conditions; New York (N.Y.) |x Social life and customs |x Pictorial works.; New York (N.Y.) |x Social life and customs |y 20th century.; New York (N.Y.) |x Social life and customs; New York (N.Y.) -- Social life and customs; Irish American women -- History -- 19th century.; Oral histories (literary works); Fulbright scholars.; War Powers Conference; New York Nichibei.; Debs, Eugene V. (Eugene Victor), 1855-1926; Tamiment Library; United States. Congress. House. |b Committee on Education and Labor; United States. Congress. House. |b Committee on Education and Labor. |b Select Subcommittee on Education; United States. Congress. House. |x Leadership; Tisch family |g [MISCELLANEOUS INFORMATION]; Tisch family |g [EVEN MORE MISCELLANEOUS INFORMATION]; Brophy, John, 1883-1963. -- |v Portraits; Carey, James B. -- |v Portraits
- Level 2 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2015-2016; mos_2024_2; 80 Washington Square East Galleries; Blaustein Family; Aaron, Florence; 23 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder handwritten notes 24" x 24"; Level 2 This is the abstract. It has a bold title in it.; Level 2 This is the Materials Specific Details. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Level 2 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
  Accruals
  Level 2 This is the Accruals note.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Level 2 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
  Appraisal
  Level 2 This is the Appraisal note.
  Arrangement
  Level 2 This is the Arrangement note.
  Historical Note
  Level 2 This is the Historical note.
  Custodial History
  Level 2 This is the Custodial History note.
  File Plan
  Level 2 This is the File Plan.
  General
  This is the Level 2 General note.
  Elmer Holmes Bobst Library
  70 Washington Square South
  2nd Floor
  New York, NY 10012
  special.collections@nyu.edu
  URL:
  ALS
  The Sally Belfrage Papers (TAM 189)
  Ardouin, Charles Nicholas Celigny. Essais sur l'histoire d'Haiti. Port-au-Prince, 1865.
  No doubt the estate has exerted a tremendous influence on the development of my character. One may walk for an hour without glimpsing another soul, which has taught me to love tranquility.
  Tamiment Library March 2021
  Abbreviation Expansion
  MIT
  Massachusetts Institute of Technology
  Oral histories (literary works) Rolodex MOS.2021 Fulbright scholars. Irish American women -- History -- 19th century.
  Other Finding Aids
  Level 2 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
  Existence and Location of Originals
  Level 2 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Level 2 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
  Related Materials
  Level 2 This is the Related Materials note.
  Scope and Contents
  Level 2 This is the Scope and Content note.
  Separated Materials
  Level 2 This is the Separated Materials note.
  This is the Index head.
  Level 2 This is the Index.
  Level 2 Index term 1
  Level 2 Index term 2
  Level 2 Index term 3
  Boston (Mass.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Irish American women -- History -- 19th century.; Oral histories (literary works); Fulbright scholars.; War Powers Conference; Tamiment Library; Belfrage family
  - Level 3 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2021; mos_2024_3; 9 to 5, National Association of Working Women (U.S.); Chen family; Adams, B. O.; 12 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder Hopefully perfectly this is correct 12" x 12"; Level 3 This is the Abstract. It has a bold title in it.; Level 3 This is the Materials Specific Details note.; Level 3 This is the Physical Description note. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Level 3 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
    Level 3 This is the Accruals note.
    Level 3 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
    Level 3 This is the Appraisal note.
    Level 3 This is the Arrangement note.
    Biographical note
    Level 3 This is the Biographical note.
    Level 3 This is the Custodial History note.
    Level 3 This is the File Plan.
    This is the Level 3 General note.
    Level 3 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
    Level 3 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
    Level 3 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
    Level 3 This is the Related Materials note.
    Level 3 This is the Scope and Content note.
    Level 3 This is the Separated Materials note.
    Index head
    Level 3 This is the Index.
    Level 3 Index item
    - Level 4 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2017-2019; mos_2024_4; Yivo Institute for Jewish Research; Pinsof family; Zwillinger, Rhonda; 2 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder This is a test 1' x 27"; Level 4 This is the Abstract.It has a bold title in it.; Level 4 This is the Materials Specific Details note.; Level 4 This is the Physical Description note. (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Level 4 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
      Level 4 This is the Accruals note.
      Level 4 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
      Level 4 This is the Appraisal note.
      Level 4 This is the Arrangement note.
      Level 4 This is the Biographical note.
      Level 4 This is the Custodial History note.
      Level 4 This is the File Plan.
      This is the Level 4 General note.
      Level 4 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
      Level 4 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
      Level 4 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
      Level 4 This is the Related Materials note.
      Level 4 This is the Scope and Content note.
      Level 4 This is the Separated Materials note.
      Level 4 This is the Index.
      Level 4 Index item
      - Level 5 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2015-2019; mos_2024_5; World Trade Center (New York, N.Y.); Draper family; Yonge, Charlotte Mary, 1823-1901; 5 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder This is still a test 7" x 45'; Level 5 This is the Abstract. It has a bold title in it.; Level 5 This is the Materials Specific Details note.; Level 5 This is the Physical Description note. (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Level 5 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
        Level 5 This is the Accruals note.
        Level 5 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
        Level 5 This is the Appraisal note.
        Level 5 This is the Arrangement note.
        Level 5 This is the Biographical note.
        Level 5 This is the Custodial History note.
        Level 5 This is the File Plan.
        This is the Level 5 General note.
        Level 5 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
        Level 5 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
        Level 5 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
        Level 5 This is the Related Materials note.
        Level 5 This is the Scope and Content note.
        Level 5 This is the Separated Materials note.
        Level 5 This is the Index.
        Level 5 Index Item
        - Level 6 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2020; mos_2024_6; Workers' Party of Ireland; Blaustein Family; Alum, Rolando A.; 3 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder This is still a test 2" x 2"; Level 6 This is the Abstract. It has a title in it.; Level 6 This is the Materials Specific Details note.; Level 6 This is the Physical Description note. (Box 1, Folder 337)
          Level 6 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
          Level 6 This is the Accruals note.
          Level 6 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
          Level 6 This is the Appraisal note.
          Level 6 This is the Arrangement note.
          Level 6 This is the Biographical note.
          Level 6 This is the Custodial History note.
          Level 6 This is the File Plan.
          This is the Level 6 General note.
          Level 6 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
          Level 6 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
          Level 6 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
          Level 6 This is the Related Materials note.
          Level 6 This is the Scope and Content note.
          Level 6 This is the Separated Materials note.
          Level 6 This is the Index.
          Level 6 Index item
          - A File Nested Within a File, No Container, 1981-08-31
  - This is an item Here is a title. There is also a name. (Box 1)
    Bibliography
    This is Not It: Stories. New York: Distributed Art Publishers, 2002.
  - The Dreaded Other Level, 1981-09-02
- Series II. Additional Digital Objects
  - Audio-Service
  - Audio-Reading-Room
  - Video-Service
  - Video-Reading-Room
  - Image-Service
  - External-Link
  - Electronic-Records-Reading-Room
  - Image-Service
  Historical/Biographical Note
  During his lifetime, Charles Butler was involved in many endeavors. For a time he was employed as an agent for the New York Life Insurance and Trust Company, and held various positions in the transportation industry working with canals, roads, and railroads. He was also involved in New York politics, anti-Masonry, and state bond investment and land speculation in the antebellum west. One such interest was in the Wabash and Erie Canal, the construction of which Congress authorized in 1827. When completed in 1853, the Wabash and Erie Canal was the longest man-made waterway in the Western Hemisphere and extended nearly 500 miles. By 1860, however, after a short time in use, the canal was incrementally abandoned in response to the proliferation of railroads.
  Butler's other accomplishments are outlined in the following chronology
  Missing Title
  Jan 15, 1802 Born, Kinderhook Landing, N.Y.
  1819 Employed as clerk in the law office of Martin Van Buren at Albany, N.Y.
  1822 Appointed deputy clerk of New York State Senate
  1824 Admitted to New York Bar
  1825 Married Eliza A. Ogden
  1826-1827 Prosecuted the kidnappers of William Morgan, a Freemason
  1829 Appointed postmaster at Geneva, N.Y.
  1830 Became an agent of the New York Life Insurance and Trust Co.
  1833 Traveled in Michigan, Indiana, and Illinois
  1834 Moved to New York City
  1836 Became a member of the Council of the University of the City of New York Became one of twenty founders of the Union Theological Seminary and a member of its first Board of Directors.
  ca. 1862 President of the St. Louis, Alton, and Terre Haute Railroad Co.
  1870-1897 President of the Board of Directors for the Union Theological Seminary
  Dec 13, 1897 Died, New York City
- ANCESTOR 1, 1111
  - 1112
    - 1113
      - LEAF 1
      - LEAF 2, 1113
      - 1113
      - 1113
- Aerial Views, 1890s, 1890-1899, 2001, undated (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1907; wsp_av_1_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking South, circa 1890; wsp_av_1_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 1, Item 2)
    Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
  - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1890; wsp_av_1_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 1, Item 3)
- New York College of Dentistry Announcement, 1911-2023-03-27; cuid18334 (Box 80, Folder 25)
- Posters, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 5-6, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Folder 1-6, Box 18, Folder 4-5, Box 19, Folder 3-13, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Folder 1-8, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Folder 1-10, Box 35, Box 36, Folder 8-9, Box 37, Box 39, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 6)
- Cars & Map
  - Subway cars >, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Subway map <, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Refractive Index of Sodium Vapor and Width of D1 in Absorptions: Apr. 1929 Dispersion and Absorption Line Width in the Alkali Vapors: Aug. 1929 A Sensitive Method for Determining Refractive Indices, SAK and J. Q. Stewart: Jun. 1930 Scattering of Light in Sodium Vapor: Jan. 1930 Distinction between Scattering and Absorption, SAK and John Q. Stewart: Jan. 1930, 1921-1930 (Box 7, Folder 14)